## Sarib Kashif

648 Trudeau Drive, Milton, ON L9T5L7 | C: 647-242-5928 | E: <u>kashifsar01@gmail.com</u> <u>github.com/SaribK</u> | <u>linkedin.com/in/sarib-kashif-6047b9192</u>

## **Summary**

Skilled Computer Programmer capable of producing code quickly and accurately. Considerably well-versed in agile methodologies and capable of working in both independent and team-based capacities. Experience in object oriented and functional programming languages. Knowledge in microeconomics and macroeconomics.

## Education

McMaster University - Hamilton, ON | Bachelor's in Applied Science Computer Science, Expected in 08/2024

# **Experience**

**CASHIER** | 06/2018 to 08/2018

Pizza Pizza - Mississauga, Ontario

Maintained high productivity by efficiently processing transactions for customers

#### **REPLENISHMENT CLERK** | 10/2018 to 04/2019

Loblaws - Milton, Ontario

Pleasantly helped customers by finding requested items, boosting store revenues and improving retention rates in a timely manner while also restocking products where necessary

# **Programming Projects**

*Battle Bots* (09/2017 – 02/2018)

- AI bot programmed in Java to shoot and dodge bullets in a group project. Created in Eclipse. *Ball Rolling Adventure Game* (02/2019 06/2019)
- 3D game with saved data on Unity using C# with a GUI, item shop, and progressing levels. *Ants vs Spiders Simulation* (02/2019 04/2019)
  - Shows how ants and spiders interact nearby in relation to land, food and dominance.

*Yahtzee Game* (04/2018 – 06/2018)

• Created my own customized version of Yahtzee with C# on Visual Studio.

*Tower Defense Game* (02/2018 – 06/2018)

- 3D game with towers shooting zombies to prevent them from reaching the main tower.
- Each tower has different abilities (ice, rapid fire, explosions) which have to be purchased.

### **Certifications**

- Cisco IT Essentials Certificate
- Cisco Cybersecurity Essentials Certificate

### Skills

- Excellent problem solving skills
- Programming and design skills
- Expertise in C#, Java, Haskell
- Good in HTML, Javascript, C/C++
- Information security

- Agile development frameworks
- Software testing and debugging
- Waterfall Model
- Team leadership
- Oral and written communications